Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Roster and price list of the Williamsport Musicians' Protective Assoc., 1947-1948 (Box 274, Folder 1)
    Author: Williamsport Musicians' Protective Association
  - Item 10: Price list - Musicians Protective Union, 1947; Publication (Box 274, Folder 1)
    Author: Musicians Protective Union
  - Item 11: Article by President James C. Petrillo, explaining the position of the American Federation of Musicians in the recording situation, 1948; Publication (Box 274, Folder 1)
    Notes: Reprinted from the Feb. 1948 issue of the International Musician. 2 copies
  - Item 12: Public Relations annual for Local Unions, 1949-1953 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Price list - Membership Directory and by-laws - Musician's Assoc. of Westchester County, 1959; Publication (Box 274, Folder 1)
    Author: Musician's Association of Westchester County
  - Item 14: Price list other than theatrical - Musical Mutual Protective Union. Local 310, 1914; Publication (Box 274, Folder 1)
    Author: Musical Mutual Protective Union. Local 310
  - Item 15: Directory, 1956-1957 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Petrillo's Case: new light on an age-old problem--man vs. machine, 1948; Publication (Box 274, Folder 1)
    Author: Milton Diamond
    Notes: Reprinted from the March 1948 issue of the International Musician. 2 copies
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Directory, 1956-1957 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Directory, 1960; Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The story of the American Federation of Musicians, 1948; Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Petrillo, 1942; Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
    Author: Robert Coughlan
    Notes: magazine article
  - Item 5: Capsule of Local 132 history by Edward J. Moore, 1976; Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Musicians Performance Trust Funds, 1956; Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Subsidy makes sense, 1961; Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
    Author: Hope Stoddard
  - Item 8: Three years of free music, 1950; Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The record on records, Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: You are your union, 1961; Publication (Box 274, Folder 2)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Directory, 1964; Publication (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Directory, 1966; Publication (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Directory, 1968; Publication (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Eventful decade: cartoonists' version of James C. Petrillo and the A.F. of M. over the last 10 years, Publication (Box 274, Folder 3)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Directory, 1967; Publication (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Directory, 1970; Publication (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Directory, 1965; Publication (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: --and the band plays on--, 1963; Publication (Box 274, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Dos & don'ts, 1955; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: No room for complacency in public relations; an address., 1954; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Author: Kelly Shugart
  - Item 3: Your place in the atom, Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: List of Locals, 1952; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Feb-52
  - Item 5: List of Locals, 1953; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: List of Locals, 1954; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Sept. 1954
  - Item 7: List of Locals, 1955; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Feb. 1955
  - Item 8: List of Locals, 1960; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Sept. 1960
  - Item 9: List of Locals, 1942; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Mar. 1942
  - Item 10: List of Locals, 1943; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Sept. 1943
  - Item 11: List of Locals, 1949; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Mar. 1949
  - Item 12: List of Locals, 1950; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jun-50
  - Item 13: List of Locals, 1951; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jul-51
  - Item 14: Souvenir - The Overture, 1954; Publication (Box 274, Folder 5)
    Notes: Presented to visitors at the Labor-Management Exposition
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Musician's Voice, 1963-1964 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 1,3-10
  - Item 2: The Musician's Voice, 1964-1965 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.2, no.1-10
  - Item 3: The Musician's Voice, 1965-1966 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.3, no.3-9
  - Item 4: The Musician's Voice, 1966-1967 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.4, no.1-6
  - Item 5: The Musician's Voice, 1967-1968 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.5, no.1-3
  - Item 6: Directory, 1977; Publication (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Directory, 1966; Publication (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Directory, 1977; Publication (Box 274, Folder 7)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Petrillo sad old times are over, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: James C. Petrillo and how he grew, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Music strike set for New Year Eve, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Musicians lift ban on Dodger Sym-Phony, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Networks to study work for musicians, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Music loser at 2,426 flail muse in weird ebbets field cacophony, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Lippert, Petrillo in accord on video, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: TV musicians win wage rise of 10%, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Court order bars picketing of work, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Petrillo bans recordings abroad ..., 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Petrillo seeking tv music control, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Met may be shut by labor dispute, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: More strikers to go back to atom plant, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Local 802 votes to stop the music, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Concert dropped in labor dispute, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Musicians union fighting for jobs, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Petrillo changes a couple of tunes, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Stokowski explains picket line crossing, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Musicians union sets up new fund, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Wor stays on air minus musicians, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: Musicians union sets up new fund, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: Mayor passes up Yankee opener bowing to musicians' picket line, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: Petrillo is tired will step down, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: Power of the public, 1951-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Musician 'Angels' barred by union, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: Petrillo blocks local 802 motion, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: Petrillo asks board to act on Davis row, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: Union rule fought on backing shows, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: Union outlaws school bands from basketball in garden, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 30: Petrillo demands US aid musicians, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 31: Petrillo urges subsidies in arts, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 32: Leview on records stir union unrest, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 33: Musicians union to shun cultural Parley..., 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 34: Protest to the Mayor by musicians' union cancels free police concerts in Queens, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 35: petrillo allocates final music fund, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 36: Musicians union loses on pickets, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 37: Petrillo to meet movie producers, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 38: Pact to lifted by Petrillo, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 39: Petrillo asks fees on TV music films, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 40: Restaurant cites high court ruling in union dispute, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 41: NLRB rules Taft-Hartley act applies to Philadelphia Symphony, 1948-1956 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 42: Musicians cleared in Taft law case, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 43: Featherbed case won by musicians, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 44: Name band leaders to hear strike plans, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 45: Musicians sign contracts to play in televised films, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 46: Petrillo suspends conductor on charge of bootlegging orchestra to evade TV ban..., 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 47: Musicians union wins court fight on hiring, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 48: Wage rise assures New Year's music, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 49: Union blacklists hotels, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 50: Musicians strike on networks set, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 51: Petrillo cancels strikes by unions, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 52: Win ends dispute with musician unit, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 53: Canned music ban on the air is asked, 1950-1953 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 54: memo to: New York State Conference Locals, 1993; Publication (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 55: Directory, 1993; Publication (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Item 56: Directory, 1975-1976 (Box 274, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The School Musician: Petrillo States his case, 1949; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Music for the people: a report by the American Federation of Musicians, 1949; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Outstanding National Service, 1938; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The music code of ethics, 1947; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: A statement of facts, 1950; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Roster and price list of the Williamsport Musicians' Protective Assoc., 1947-1948 (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Price list - Musicians Protective Union, 1947; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Article by President James C. Petrillo, explaining the position of the American Federation of Musicians in the recording situation, 1948; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Public Relations annual for Local Unions, 1949-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Price list - Membership Directory and by-laws - Musician's Assoc. of Westchester County, 1959; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Price list other than theatrical - Musical Mutual Protective Union. Local 310, 1914; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Directory, 1956-1957 (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Petrillo's Case: new light on an age-old problem--man vs. machine, 1948; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The story of the American Federation of Musicians, 1948; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Petrillo, 1942; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Capsule of Local 132 history by Edward J. Moore, 1976; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Musicians Performance Trust Funds, 1956; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Subsidy makes sense, 1961; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Three years of free music, 1950; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The record on records, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: You are your union, 1961; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 2)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Eventful decade: cartoonists' version of James C. Petrillo and the A.F. of M. over the last 10 years, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 3)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: --and the band plays on--, 1963; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Dos & don'ts, 1955; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: No room for complacency in public relations; an address., 1954; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Your place in the atom, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Souvenir - The Overture, 1954; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The record on records, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Subsidy makes sense, 1961; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Musician's Voice, 1963-1964 (Box 274.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The Musician's Voice, 1964-1965 (Box 274.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The Musician's Voice, 1965-1966 (Box 274.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The Musician's Voice, 1966-1967 (Box 274.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: The Musician's Voice, 1967-1968 (Box 274.1, Folder 7)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Petrillo sad old times are over, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: James C. Petrillo and how he grew, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Music strike set for New Year Eve, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Musicians lift ban on Dodger Sym-Phony, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Networks to study work for musicians, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Music loser at 2,426 flail muse in weird ebbets field cacophony, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Lippert, Petrillo in accord on video, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: TV musicians win wage rise of 10%, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Court order bars picketing of work, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Petrillo bans recordings abroad ..., 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Petrillo seeking tv music control, 1950-1951 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Met may be shut by labor dispute, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: More strikers to go back to atom plant, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Local 802 votes to stop the music, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Concert dropped in labor dispute, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Musicians union fighting for jobs, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Petrillo changes a couple of tunes, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Stokowski explains picket line crossing, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Musicians union sets up new fund, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Wor stays on air minus musicians, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: Musicians union sets up new fund, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: Mayor passes up Yankee opener bowing to musicians' picket line, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: Petrillo is tired will step down, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: Power of the public, 1951-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Musician 'Angels' barred by union, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: Petrillo blocks local 802 motion, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: Petrillo asks board to act on Davis row, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: Union rule fought on backing shows, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: Union outlaws school bands from basketball in garden, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 30: Petrillo demands US aid musicians, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 31: Petrillo urges subsidies in arts, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 32: Leview on records stir union unrest, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 33: Musicians union to shun cultural Parley..., 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 34: Protest to the Mayor by musicians' union cancels free police concerts in Queens, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 35: petrillo allocates final music fund, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 36: Musicians union loses on pickets, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 37: Petrillo to meet movie producers, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 38: Pact to lifted by Petrillo, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 39: Petrillo asks fees on TV music films, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 40: Restaurant cites high court ruling in union dispute, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 41: NLRB rules Taft-Hartley act applies to Philadelphia Symphony, 1948-1956 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 42: Musicians cleared in Taft law case, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 43: Featherbed case won by musicians, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 44: Name band leaders to hear strike plans, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 45: Musicians sign contracts to play in televised films, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 46: Petrillo suspends conductor on charge of bootlegging orchestra to evade TV ban..., 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 47: Musicians union wins court fight on hiring, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 48: Wage rise assures New Year's music, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 49: Union blacklists hotels, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 50: Musicians strike on networks set, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 51: Petrillo cancels strikes by unions, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 52: Win ends dispute with musician unit, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 53: Canned music ban on the air is asked, 1950-1953 (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 54: memo to: New York State Conference Locals, 1993; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 55: Directory, 1993; Publication (Box 274.1, Folder 8)
- National Air Traffic Controllers Association MEBA/AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: flyer and correspondence, 1987; Publication (Box 275, Folder 1)
- Thomas Kennedy, Publication (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The role of labor in early American history, 1932; Publication (Box 275, Folder 2)
- National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, Publication (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1961-1965 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Forgotten ones, 1963; Publication (Box 275, Folder 3)
    Author: Daniel Panger
  - Item 3: The Forgotten People, 1962; Publication (Box 275, Folder 3)
    Author: Dale Wright
  - Item 4: New Hope for Braceros, 1964; Publication (Box 275, Folder 3)
    Author: Max Awner
  - Item 5: Poverty on the land in a land of plenty, 1964; Publication (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Below the poverty level, 1960-1969 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Public Law 78, how it works, 1960-1969 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: America's displace persons, 1960-1969 (Box 275, Folder 3)
- National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, Publication (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agribusiness and its workers, 1963; Publication (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Farm labor organizing, 1905-1967, Publication (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The grape strike, 1966; Publication (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The case for the domestic farm worker, 1965; Publication (Box 275, Folder 4)
- National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, Publication (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The position of farm workers in Federal and State legislation, 1959; Publication (Box 275, Folder 5)
    Author: Robin Myers
  - Item 2: Louisiana story, 1964; the sugar system and the plantation workers., Publication (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Report on farm labor: public hearings of the National Advisory Committee on farm Labor, Washington, D. C., Feb. 5 and 6, 1959, Publication (Box 275, Folder 5)
    Author: National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor (U.S.)
- National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, Publication (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Summary of public hearings, 1959; Publication (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Testimony by J.W. GrantHow Conditions for farm labor have been improved in the Pacific Northwest, 1959; Publication (Box 275, Folder 6)
    Author: J. W. Grant
  - Item 3: Hearings - Testimony by the following - George Stith; Statements by -William F. Schnitzler; H.L. Mitchell; Reuben Johnson; Dr. Hecotr Garcia; George T. Dowdy; Delmer Berg; Raul Aguilar, Publication (Box 275, Folder 6)
    Author: George Stith; William F. Schnitzle; H.L. Mitchell; Reuben Johnson; Dr. Hecotr Garcia; George T. Dowdy; Delmer Berg; Raul Aguilar
  - Item 4: Equal protection of the law, 1959; Publication (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Statement of K.P. Thornton, 1959; Publication (Box 275, Folder 6)
    Author: K. P. Thornton
  - Item 6: California's captive farm workers, 1959; Publication (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: America fails the farm worker, 1959; Publication (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Testimony prepared for National Advisory.., regarding American Friends Service Committee Experience in work with Seasonal Farm Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 275, Folder 6)
- National Labor-Management Foundation, Publication (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Rules of order, simplified, 1960; Publication (Box 276, Folder 1)
- National Labor Bureau, Publication (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Economic Counsel for labor unions, 1945; Publication (Box 276, Folder 2)
- National Institute of Labor Education (U.S.), Publication (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: National Institute of Labor Education, Publication (Box 276, Folder 3)
- National Independent Union Council, Publication (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the 1961 convention, Publication (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Resolutions from the 1962 convention, Publication (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Minutes of the 1961 Legislative Conference of the, 1962; Publication (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Constitution. As amended at the 1960 & 1962 conventions (Box 276, Folder 4)
- National Council on Agricultural Life and Labor, Publication (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1957; Publication (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: How migratory farm labor fared in the eighty-seventh congress, 1962; Publication (Box 276, Folder 5)
- Straight Talk, Publication (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Straight Talk, 1961-1962 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 1-6
  - Item 2: Straight Talk, 1962-1963 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 1-6
  - Item 3: Straight Talk, 1963-1964 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 1-2, 4, 4A-6
  - Item 4: Straight Talk, 1964-1965 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 5, no. 1, 3, 5-6
  - Item 5: Aerospace workers for freedom, Publication (Box 276, Folder 6)
- National Institute of Labor Education (U.S.), Publication (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Press release, 1957; Publication (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: A world of new service for you, Publication (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Resolution on Labor Extension Service, Publication (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: American Workers Want a Labor Extension Service!, Publication (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: American workers want a labor extension service!, 1946; Publication (Box 276, Folder 7)
- American Jewish Committee, Publication (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Working for labor: the story of the National Labor Service, founded to promote good will among American workers of all races and religions, Publication (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: We open the gates: labor's fight for equality, 1958; Publication (Box 276, Folder 8)
    Author: Harry Fleischman
  - Item 3: article reprinted from the New York Times Magazine - Discrimination hurts you, Publication (Box 276, Folder 8)